Guide to the Zaki Nusseibeh Collection of photographs AD.MC.020
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
Zaki Nusseibeh Collection
1940s-1980s
1970-1980
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
AD.MC.020
149 Photographic Prints
The Zaki Nusseibeh Collection is a series of photographs from the private library of His Excellency Zaki Nusseibeh, UAE Minister of State. The photographs are an insightful window into an Abu Dhabi as the city took its first steps toward becoming the burgeoning commercial and cultural center it is today. In addition, they reveal an intimate and unique view into the public life of the late Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan. Mr. Nusseibeh was a key aide to His Highness Sheikh Zayed as an advisor and interpreter among many other roles, and his personal collection of photographs reflect his dedicated service to the nation's founder. The Zaki Nusseibeh Collection is a celebration of the UAE in its inception - we see the buildings of the modern city of Abu Dhabi rise in the nineteen-sixties and seventies, as Sheikh Zayed visited countries throughout the world and hosted foreign leaders at home in the UAE. The Collection brings the viewer into the eighties as well, with candid images of other honored Emirati leaders including HH Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan and HH Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed al Nahyan. Akkasah is honored to invite the world to view this enlightening collection of images, made possible by the generosity of HE Zaki Nusseibeh.
Box Digital copy only
Biographical / Historical
Zaki Nusseibeh was born in Jerusalem, studied there and in Cambridge University, UK, gaining a Masters degree in Economics. He moved to Abu Dhabi in 1967 and became Sheikh Zayed's personal translator in 1968 being bestowed UAE citizenship shortly afterwards.
He has held various positions within the Abu Dhabi government including Director of Information, Director of the Press Office for HH the President, Assistant Minister of Foreign Affairs and International Co-operation and Cultural Advisor at the Ministry of Presidential Affairs, Deputy Chairman of the Abu Dhabi Culture and Heritage Authority, and most recently Minister of State. He has also served on numerous boards, including; Chairman of the London School of Economics LSE Middle East Centre Advisory Board and member of London School of Oriental and African Studies SOAS Middle East Centre Advisory Board, and of the Alliance Française Foundation in Paris. He was also the President of the Alliance Francaise Abu Dhabi and the UAE chapter of the International 'Friends of Richard Wagner' society. He helped in founding the Abu Dhabi Classics program in Abu Dhabi and the Al Ain Music Festival in Al Ain. In 2014 he was also asked to chair the Wagner Foundation in Leipzig, Germany and is a member on the Board of Trustees of the Agha Khan Museum in Toronto and of the Institut du Monde Arabe in Paris.
Content Description
The Zaki Nusseibeh Collection comprises of 149 gelatin silver prints scanned at 400ppi, they are mainly press shots of Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh on numerous state visits including to India, Pakistan, Morocco, France, the USA and UK. There are also some photographs of buildings and streets in Abu Dhabi and Al Ain, the bulk of the images are dated between 1970-1980.
Arrangement
This collection has been processed as it was received.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Original photographs were obtained directly from Zaki Nusseibeh, digitized, and returned.
Scope and Contents
The Zaki Nusseibeh Collection comprises of scans of 149 photographic prints from the library of Zaki Nusseibeh, an Emirati Minister of State. The photographs represent a number of setting inside and outside the United Arab Emirates between the early 1950's and 1990's. Notable subjects are Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed Al Nahyan meeting with a number of notable world leaders and dignitaries from throughout the world, and images of the building of infrastructure in Abu Dhabi from the 1960's into the 1980's.
United Arab Emirates; Royalty; Press Photography; Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; India; Pakistan; England, UK; Political Leadership
- A mosque in Abu Dhabi., Circa 1970; ref1; 1 Photographic Prints; 1 (Box Digital copy only)
  Architecture; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Mosques; Gelatin Silver Prints; Religious Sites; Photographic Prints
- A group performing the Al Ayala dance., Circa 1970; ref2; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Regional/National Dress; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Police; Dancing; Regional/National Dress; Men; Girls; Audiences/Spectators; Canes/Walking Sticks; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Weapons; Guns; Outdoors; Children; Women; Group Portraits
- Clock Tower roundabout on Corniche Street., Circa 1970; ref3; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Clocks/Watches; Boats/Ships; Street Lamps; Coast; Transportation
- Trucks at a loading dock at the Abu Dhabi port., Circa 1970; ref4; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cars/Trucks; Ports; Boats/Ships; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Transportation; Outdoors
- Boats on a coastline., Circa 1970; ref5; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boats/Ships; Men; Water; Coast; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Transportation; Arabian/Persian Gulf; Outdoors
- A Rolls Royce belonging to Sheikh Zayed in downtown Abu Dhabi., Circa 1970; ref6; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Cars/Trucks; Buildings; Transportation; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Gardeners in a park., Circa 1970; ref7; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Water; Gardens; Workers; Parks; Men; Street Lamps; Outdoors; Group Portraits
- Minaret of Sheikh Zayed the Second Mosque in Abu Dhabi., Circa 1970; ref8; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Mosques; Buildings; Architecture; Religious Sites
- Scaffolding surrounding a street light on Corniche road., Circa 1970; ref9; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Flags; Street Lamps; Streets/Roads; Men; Buildings; Workers; Outdoors; Coast
- A street view with Al Firdous open air cinema in the background., Circa 1970; ref10; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps; Cars/Trucks; Buildings; Cinema; Transportation; Signs/Signposts; Advertisements
- Souq Al Markezi in Abu Dhabi., Circa 1970; ref11; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Signs/Signposts; Shops; Markets; Men; Buildings; Regional/National Dress; Crowds; Regional/National Dress; Arabic Writing; English Writing; Flags; Outdoors
- Street photographer with a wet process camera., Circa 1970s; ref12; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Men; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Cameras; Street Vendors; Outdoors; Group Portraits
- A street view with the Grindlays Bank building in the foreground., Circa 1970s; ref13; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps; Signs/Signposts; Signs/Signposts; Shops; Architecture; Buildings; Banks; Flags
- Al Fahim mosque at the junction of the roads then known as Khalifa Street, Al Istiqlal Street and Airport Road., Circa 1970s; ref14; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Mosques; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Men; Arabic Calligraphy; Shops; Religious Sites
- Two boys riding a horse and a boy walking with them., Circa 1970s; ref15; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Boys; Horses; Animals; Deserts; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Outdoors; Group Portraits
- Men walking on the side of the Corniche., Circa 1970s; ref16; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Coast; Men; Canes/Walking Sticks; Water; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Arabian/Persian Gulf; Outdoors; Group Portraits
- Central Abu Dhabi, Sheikh Hamdan Street., Circa 1970s; ref17; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Cars/Trucks; Street Lamps; Signs/Signposts; Architecture; Buildings; Transportation; Shops
- A woman carrying a basket on her head., Circa 1970s; ref18; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Cars/Trucks; Women; Men; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Machines; Outdoors; Group Portraits
- A wind tower., Circa 1970s; ref19; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Buildings
- National Bank of Abu Dhabi on Khalifa street., Circa 1970s; ref20; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Banks; Buildings; Architecture; Cars/Trucks; Flags; Signs/Signposts; Transportation
- Energy plant in Al Khalidiya., Circa 1970s; ref21; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Factories; Construction; Street Lamps; Buildings
- A portrait of Sheikh Zayed., Circa 1970s; ref22; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Individual Portraits; Political Leadership; Regional/National Dress; Men; Royalty; Presidents; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- A gravel depot with trucks in the background., Circa 1970s; ref23; 1 Photographic Prints 22.2 x 30 cm (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Cars/Trucks; Workers; Men; Transportation; Outdoors
- Street view with Rolls Royce belonging to Sheikh Zayed., Circa 1970s; ref24; 1 Photographic Prints 21 x 29.7 cm (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Cars/Trucks; Signs/Signposts; Architecture; Buildings; Transportation; Street Lamps; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Kentucky Fried Chicken and Wimpy building next to Al Bateen Airport., Circa 1970s; ref25; 1 Photographic Prints 22.2 x 29.6 cm (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Restaurants/bars; Street Lamps; Parks; Signs/Signposts; Streets/Roads; Architecture; Buildings; Restaurants/bars; Arabic Writing; English Writing
- A man standing on a concrete wall., Circa 1970s; ref26; 1 Photographic Prints 22.3 x 30 cm (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Cars/Trucks; Men; Ports; Construction; Transportation; Outdoors; Individual Portraits
- People at the Corniche., Circa 1970s; ref27; 1 Photographic Prints 21.7 x 30.4 cm (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Children; Boys; Girls; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Water; Arabian/Persian Gulf; Outdoors; Coast; Group Portraits
- Al Ain during the union with the Clock Tower in the background., Circa 1970s; ref28; 1 Photographic Prints 21.1 x 29.7 cm (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches; Monuments/Memorials; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Signs/Signposts; Street Lamps; Streets/Roads
- Hilton Al Ain with tents in the foreground., Circa 1970s; ref29; 1 Photographic Prints 21 x 29.5 cm (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Hotels; Tents; Buildings; Architecture; Street Lamps; Electricity
- Zayed Port taken from motor boat., Circa 1970s; ref30; 1 Photographic Prints 22.1 x 29.9 cm (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Water; Arabian/Persian Gulf; Boats/Ships; Men; Ports; Transportation
- Helicopter at Hilton Al Ain., Circa 1970s; ref31; 1 Photographic Prints 22.3 x 29.9 cm (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Hotels; Transportation; Cars/Trucks; Airplanes; Buildings; Architecture
- An abacus in a classroom., Circa 1970s; ref32; 1 Photographic Prints 21.1 x 29.6 cm (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Children; Girls; Uniforms; Pens/Inkwells; Schools/Education; Individual Portraits
- Central Abu Dhabi with the Banque de Paris et des Paybas and Mohammed Rasool Khoury & Sons buildings on Airport road., Circa 1970; ref33; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps; Cars/Trucks; Signs/Signposts; Buildings; Architecture; Construction; Banks; Shops; Transportation; Advertisements; English Writing
- Falcon statue., Circa 1970; ref34; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Statues/Sculptures; Buildings; Arabic Writing
- Qasr Al Hosn., Circa 1970; ref35; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Buildings; Forts/Castles
- Khalidiya Palace Hotel., Circa 1970; ref36; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Buildings; Street Lamps; Hotels; Irrigation
- View of Hamdan Street., Circa 1970; ref37; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Signs/Signposts; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps; Men; Buildings; Construction; Architecture; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Flags; Outdoors
- An external view of stables with horses., Circa 1970; ref38; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Architecture; Horses; Deserts; Animals
- Zaki Nusseibeh by Rene Burri., 20 October 1974; ref39; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Telephones; Individual Portraits; French Writing; Furnishings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Offices; Men
- A portrait of Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1970; ref40; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Individual Portraits; Men
- Abu Dhabi Police headquarters opposite Qasr Al Hosn., Circa 1970; ref41; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Cars/Trucks; Men; Uniforms; Weapons; Guns; Buildings; Police; Regional/National Dress; Transportation; Outdoors; Canes/Walking Sticks; Group Portraits
- Zaki Nusseibeh working on an airplane., Circa 1970; ref42; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Airplanes; Transportation; Pens/Inkwells; Clocks/Watches; Individual Portraits
- Studio portrait of young Zaki Nusseibeh holding a camera with a child., Circa 1950; ref43; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Children; Boys; Cameras
- A studio portrait of a young Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1950; ref44; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Children
- Sheikh Zayed shaking hands with Zaki Nusseibeh (right)., Circa 1970; ref45; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Uniforms; Police; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Presidents; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Five men with rifles seated on a sofa., Circa 1970; ref46; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Guns; Regional/National Dress; Weapons; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
- Sheikh Zayed seated in a gathering., Circa 1970; ref47; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Audiences/Spectators; Regional/National Dress; Men; Binoculars; Women; Political Leadership; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Portrait of Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1970; ref48; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Individual Portraits; Pens/Inkwells; Offices
- Sheikh Zayed seated in a gathering., Circa 1970; ref49; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Crowds; Men; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Royalty
- Sheikh Zayed and a group of men in front of Al Bateen Airport., Circa 1970; ref50; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Airports; Men; Cars/Trucks; Flags; Buildings; Uniforms; Police; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Transportation; Arabic Writing; English Writing; Outdoors; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Zaki Nusseibeh sitting at a desk., Circa 1970; ref51; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Individual Portraits; Offices; Cigarettes; Offices; Telephones; Furnishings; Newspapers/Magazines; Buildings
- A studio portrait of a young Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1950; ref52; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Unknown Locations; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Boys; Men; Buildings
- Abu Dhabi Police band in Qasr Al Hosn., 1963; ref53; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Boys; Crowds; Uniforms; Marching Band; Police; Forts/Castles; Architecture; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Outdoors; Group Portraits
- Group portrait of the First Abu Dhabi Police Band., 1963; ref54; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Police; Uniforms; Marching Band; Arabic Writing; Children; Regional/National Dress; Streets/Roads; Facial Hair
- Boats at the Dubai creek., Circa 1970; ref55; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Boats/Ships; Water; Cars/Trucks; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Construction; Men; Transportation
- A view of oil drilling rig from below., Circa 1970; ref56; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Machines; Petroleum industry and trade.
- A ferris wheel with a portrait of Sheikh Zayed in the middle., Circa 1970; ref57; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Paintings; Royalty; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed with British Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher and Zaki Nusseibeh (center) during her visit to UAE., 1981; ref58; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Gloves; Bags/Purses; Jewelry; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Thatcher, Margaret, 1925-2013
- Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan with Queen Elizabeth and Zaki Nusseibeh (center)., Circa 1970; ref59; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Royalty; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gloves; Hats; Bags/Purses; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Khalifa bin Zayed bin Khalifa Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1948-2022; Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, 1926-2022
- Princess Diana and Prince Charles in the UAE seating next to Sheikh Nahyan bin Mubarak and Sheikh Tahnoon bin Mohammed Al Nahyan., 1989; ref60; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Royalty; Crowds; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Televisions; Furnishings; Food; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Political Leadership; Diana, Princess of Wales, 1961-1997; Charles III, King of Great Britain, 1948-
- Princess Diana and Zaki Nusseibeh (center, wearing sunglasses)., 1989; ref61; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Men; Women; Royalty; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Jewelry; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Political Leadership; Diana, Princess of Wales, 1961-1997
- Princess Diana, Prince Charles, Sheikh Tahnoon bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, Sheikh Nahyan bin Mubarak Al Nahyan and Zaki Nusseibeh (front, wearing a black suit)., 1989; ref62; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Crowds; Cars/Trucks; Regional/National Dress; Royalty; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Police; Transportation; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Political Leadership; Diana, Princess of Wales, 1961-1997; Charles III, King of Great Britain, 1948-
- Sheikh Zayed with Prince Charles and Princess Diana and Zaki Nusseibeh (second from the left)., 1989; ref63; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Women; Men; Regional/National Dress; Royalty; Weapons; Guns; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Bags/Purses; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Charles III, King of Great Britain, 1948-; Diana, Princess of Wales, 1961-1997